so the account is not looking that good
right now you guys can see that we are
currently down about $32 on the account
ladies and gentlemen I'm sorry to
announce
that I'm going to try and turn these
$100 into a million and we got to hurry
up because the market is officially open
9:45 on Monday and we already have the
account ready to go so obviously with
one go you can't turn $100 into a
million so this is how I'm going to do
it so I'm going to be doing it one week
at a time so week one is to turn
$10000 week 2 200 400 week 3 400 800 and
pretty much scale every single week like
that that is going to be key to have the
compound interest grow with the account
because with one shot 100 to a million
it's imposs so we slowly have to scale
the account but the goal is to actually
double up the account every single week
as I tried this last time and failed and
if I double up correctly every single
week according to my calculations we
should be at a million in about three
and a half to 4 months if I use a
minimum of a 1 to2 risk reward and I
stick to 1 to two trads but this all
going to make sense in just a second and
to guarantee my success in this
Challenge and not blow it like the last
one I've set some rules in place and
these rules are the following and the
first is going to be that I can only
trade the Foreign Exchange Market I
cannot trade the stock market crypto
Market none of those only the Foreign
Exchange Market second is that every
single trade that I take I have to
publicly share with you guys in my free
telegram on my Instagram Discord YouTube
here with you guys absolutely everywhere
so you guys can see the trades real time
the before the during and the after and
you guys can capitalize off these trades
with me and then the third is that I
cannot use anybody else's traits I can
only use my own analysis using my own
strategy I cannot use any signal
providers anybody in my community nobody
only my analysis to get this Challenge
and succeed and with that being said let
the challenge begin all right so we got
to get right into this because we are
currently late so yesterday it was
actually my birthday so well right now
it's 9:54 in the morning Monday morning
woke up a little bit late because it was
my birthday yesterday so I officially
now 24 I'm no longer young now I feel
old as [__] but doesn't matter let's get
right into this market right here so
we're going to start off the challenge
on GBP JPY so actively right now for
this week we only have one two three and
four pairs of Interest obviously I
analyze a bunch of different markets you
guys can see right here I pretty much
analyze all of these markets when I
pretty much look for the opportunities
for the week ahead but I only found good
opportunities in four markets for this
week so the first one is going to be GBP
JPY so this is currently what the 4our
time frame looks like and it's giving me
a very clear indication of a reversal
pattern So currently right now this is
the daily time frame as you guys can see
up here to the top top left corner uh
and this is currently having a very
clear bullish move to the upside we've
had very clean higher lows and then a
very big higher high if you look at this
on the weekly time frame you can see
that we are now flicking over to the
weekly time frame we've had a very high
move and then a weekly dogee usually
what happens after a very strong push is
then you're going to have a retracement
now this trade that we're about to take
and it sucks that we're about to start
The Challenge on something like this is
a counter Trend trade this is a red flag
this is a no because you want to be
trading with the trend but I don't know
if because I analyzed the markets two
weeks ago before I decided to start this
Challenge and they were great and come
this week and there's not that many
great opportunities but it's okay we can
still actually make money cuz we're
going to follow the trading plan so you
can clearly see how the daily time frame
has then shifted bearish and then how
the 4H hour time frame which is this one
right here we are creating what looks to
be like a head and the shoulders pattern
so this head and shoulders pattern has
very clear done a reversal now the only
way I would look to sell is if we retest
this level of resistance and support
again clearly whenever we're under we're
selling whenever we're above we're
buying and whenever we're under we are
selling so I just want price to have a
pull back into here again to then head
to the downside so that is the first
pair GBP JPY this is my second pair it
is going to be
gbpusd so gbpusd currently right now on
the daily time frame is looking like a
very strong higher high push so you can
see this Market has had a very very
strong push to the upside now the key
that you want to do with this is you
want to continue to buy but in order for
you to continue buying with this you are
then to have need a deeper pull back
into here to then head to the upside but
this deeper pullback you can actually
trade that against the trend now it's
not ideal I repeat it highrisk trade I
don't want to do it but we're obviously
taking highrisk trades on this $100
account to then flip it and it's what
it's what the opportunity the market is
giving us currently right now because if
not I would probably not trade this week
by the way the market is looking and I
do want to get involved and if I could
find a good probability trade setup
remember the key to flipping this
account is going to be to only finding
really really really really good
probability trade setups so we go down
to the and well back to the Daily time
frame you can see this daily time frame
that line right there if I were to look
left you can see how it is a very well
respected level of resistance all
throughout here so you see very strong
level of support and then used as
resistance so when I go down to the 1H
hour time frame 1 hour time frame we
have a very strong accumulation level at
that resistance point so the only way I
would actually trade this is if we were
to have a break retest out of that zone
so that is going to confirm to us that
the daily time frame has had the higher
high and now we are going to potentially
have that retracement and if the 1 hour
breaks out of this consolidation box
it's going to confirm to me that we are
then going to have this pullback for
then the daily time frame so this is
what it would look like on the daily it
would look like one big pullback but on
the 1 hour there's going to be
opportunities on the lower time frame
you know we got to see things for the
future next is going to be Euro GBP so
Euro GBP currently right now we have had
a very strong bearish move to the
downside lower low lower high lower low
and we are now under this level of
support now we're going to be using it
as resistance daily time frame we have
clearly broken under this level of
support and now we're pretty much just
waiting for it to use it as resistance
so we're literally waiting for this
trade right here this is a trade that we
actually missed last week and this is a
beautiful l left head right shoulder
retested the neckline and then sell the
trade did not activate our entry by one
and a half Pips because we just simply
didn't have it so sucks it is what it is
that trade what we do is since we did
not execute it what we do is we just
remove it so right now what we are
waiting for on Euro gvp on the 4 Hour so
you can see that we're on the 4 Hour up
here we are then going to actually wait
for a pull back into this level we're
going to wait for price to have a pull
back to here so then we we can actually
head to the downside so you're gvp just
waiting for a 4H hour pullback have to
be patient and then lastly is going to
be GBP CAD so this is currently GBP CAD
if you notice we're literally trading
the Great British pound throughout the
whole entire week because it's the
markets that are giving me the best
opportunities so same thing as
gbpusd the great uh GBP CAD is at a very
strong higher high and if you notice
whenever the market has a strong higher
high push it has a retracement strong
higher high push retracement now we have
a really strong higher high push we are
destined for that retracement so what
I'm going to wait for is any indications
on that reversal and I'm then going to
enter the trade so now we're on the 1
hour time frame on GBP Cad and what I'm
going to be waiting for is for price to
then have a break and retest under this
structure level right here going to be
waiting for a break and retest in order
to actually enter this trade isz then it
confirms that it's shifting out of this
bullish move to then head to the
downside so everything we got this week
so far is a counter Trend trade except
your GBP but all we got to do is just be
patient and uh if we blow the account
just do it again oh and this time we're
not [__] around we got four phones
this time 1 two 3 four phones to
literally track everything for you guys
my FX book once again it's Monday
morning currently 10: in the morning and
then you guys can see the account is
currently at
$100 let the challenge begin
[Music]
holy [__] I hate egg so we just finished
Sunday Swings with the guys and one of
the guys actually told me I was just
reading right now in the Discord that
literally two of the markets that I
started off the challenge with last year
in the last challenge are the same
markets that I started off this year so
I want to go make sure and see of that
right now just going to cook some eggs
first chef is not here anymore now we
got to cook ourselves we might get a new
Chef very very very soon I literally had
to come and watch this so look 11 months
ago you can clearly see this guy right
here which by the way I don't know who
this guy is or who he thinks he is
wearing three chains look at him bro who
did I think I was wearing three chains I
look at these videos like cringe cuz I
not that person anymore but you can see
right here in the markets actually so
the first two pairs were actually GBP
Cad and
gbpusd for this time around literally a
year later when we're doing the
challenge it's actually the second pair
and then the third pair which is
actually pretty crazy oh and by the way
I have to show you guys the my effect
book account you guys can see right here
so this is the 100 to the mill accounts
we are I'm just hiding it so you guys
can see that it is clearly a real
account so this is where we're pretty
much going to track everything on this
account and I forgot as was watching the
100 to the mill series I'm like wait I
have the account but I haven't connected
it to my fbook so we just did that right
now so with that being said let's see
where today takes us
all right so right now trade update damn
that's crazy that I'm saying that right
now trade update that feels good I
haven't said that in a long time right
now it's currently 3:35 in the afternoon
markets are slow haven't really moved so
right now we're going to go hit the gym
the Cyber truck so got to do some h r
[__] all right so what I was saying is
there's something different that I want
to do with this challenge is keep a
perfect balance
not be I don't want to get drained I
don't want to get burnt out of the
challenge so what I'm going to do is
actually stay in my routine doing my
business meetings go to the gym go out
before what I would do I would just stay
up 24/7 throughout the whole week and I
was burnt out the weekends I would just
catch up on sleep and then do it again
in the last Challenge and that's
probably the main reason why I was burnt
out and blew it this time that is not
going to happen I'm going to get
shredded during this challenge cuz it's
also a financial challenge but a
physical challenge because I really do
think that I can get to the best Point
I've ever physically been in my life so
that's where we're going to be hitting
the gym cardio doing everything the
challenge for the 100 100 to the mill
just a little cherry on
[Music]
top so I have a theory right every
single time I am going to go eat at a
restaurant first of all I need a chef
badly because I hate ordering food and I
hate cooking I just need a chef but now
we got to improvise and this guy behind
the camera eats a thousand times more
than I do so I got to order for 10 for
this guy but I have a theory right if
you're going to go eat at a new
restaurant just order everything on the
menu don't order one thing because let's
say you don't like that one thing then
you got to go back and then let's say
you go back and then you don't like that
other thing again you just wasted two
trips to a place that you never liked
I'm not that guy I'm the guy that I will
order everything in one shot so I'm
going to get right now a juice a pizza a
tuna tartar one kinoa rice one panini
sandwich another
kinoa cuz [__] it right so I'm going
literally just
try a little bit of everything and then
if I like it well then I go back if I
don't like it I never go back all right
so food just got here we're very
strategic with it we order the Uber Eats
on the way home because as soon as we
get here you know traffic food gets here
same time genius so we got
whatever this is what the [__] is this
bro what is that bro I would never eat
that I didn't know the bone was black I
would have known I would have picked it
you have something against black buns um
not necessarily well that doesn't look
that attractive here Panini I don't know
explain this to me sat the chips this
right here was
$25 we got to go run later we got to
burn this out
[Music]
every day jog minimum 20 minutes trying
to lose this right
here and the only way to sweat that
piece out is by
running this
sucks hey you got to do what you got to
do all right so we just got back from
the jog currently right now it is 10:00
at night and you guys can see the first
notification right here is a GB py alert
so what I do is strategically I set my
alert at an area of Interest where I'm
looking to enter the trade so then I can
actually execute it so this actually
happened 40 minutes ago this literally
happened as soon as we left for the jog
which is annoying because I wasn't
notified 40 minutes ago I go now to
trading view which we can come here and
check it out you guys can see how
currently we are pulling up to that zone
right now so right now what I'm going to
do is shower and then I'm I'm going to
pretty much get ready to enter this
trade cuz I think it might be ready
tonight I think we're going to enter the
first trade tonight bro on the first day
on the first day yeah I know it's kind
of crazy um but I'm not in a rush as you
can tell last time what I would be doing
I would ler be like running up the
stairs to go take a trade I know this is
not going to move within the next 2 3
hours because it's 10:00 London session
starts around 2: to 3: in the morning
here so there won't be any volume until
then so now I'm just going to shower I'm
out here just waiting for the sweat to
dry up a little bit if we ran I got I
got a I got a [__] so now we're tracking
our performance with our health and our
sleep I'm going to show you guys cuz bro
last time that [__] was bad I was
sleeping like 2 3 hours now I'm going to
literally show you guys working out and
I am actively up to date with the health
health is everything if your health is
good money will come if you're
consistent with the gym you'll be
consistent with the [__] that you got to
do to get money so we'll tune in
probably back in in an hour you do
realize this is the most important trade
of the whole challenge yeah I know right
the first one is the most [__]
important trade I'm treating it like uh
cuz it is it's like I mean I I guess it
is exciting but like dude we've done
this already it's not our [__] first
time bro we got this bro you know come
on all right guys so market update it is
currently 1 in the morning and honestly
it looks like we're going to have to
trade London session tonight I took a
nap earlier caught me taking a nap so it
looks like I'm going might have to trade
L session I don't want to do this but
I'm not tired I'm not you know forcing
myself St to stay up fall asleep fall
asleep miss a trade no big deal let's
come over here to the phones and you can
see that on the Android uh it's not one
in the morning cuz this time is wrong
but $100 account this is the same
account right here you can see it's 1:00
in the morning and then this is my fbook
as well as 1:00 in the morning showing
you guys the balance of the whole entire
account so I'm showing you guys the
tracking of the account on different
phones and multiple different platforms
and different types of phones so you
guys can literally not have any doubts
about the challenge I'm sh you guys how
legit this is because seems like
nobody's able to do it this legit so
they actually come over here to the
markets and we have GBP JPY which
earlier we had the notification of price
reaching our area of Interest which was
this alarm right around here so price
notified us that price reached to that
point so now that we're here and we've
had the pullback that I've been
anticipating I go down to then the lower
time Fram such as the 1 hour and I'm
going to be looking for a bearish
engulfing area at this level something
like this right here this is a beautiful
bearish engulfing ing Candlestick
engulfing the previous one look at that
beautiful move to then the downside so
I'm going to be looking for price to
engulf this Candlestick right here the
bottom of that Candlestick if it engulfs
it I'll pretty much be looking to enter
the trade and then I would have my stop
loss right around here and then probably
my take profit right around somewhere
here I would have a minimum of a 1 to
two or 1 to
2.5 risk to reward ratio so let say
session is probably going to start in
about an hour and a half more or less if
I stay up I catch it if I don't I don't
it is what it is if I don't get that
beish engulfing candles stick I will not
enter the trade I'm going to be very
patient because the first trade is
pretty much the most important one it's
going to get me out of the hole so I'm
going to be very selective on the first
trade let's go look at the other markets
actually so next Market is
gbpusd and you guys can see how earlier
today this Market was literally at the
High and the high of this Market is
where we were anticipating for price to
break and retest under the zone so we
actually hit the bottom of that zone and
we weren't able to actually retest it
this is what it looks like on the daily
so the daily looks like it has a very
nice daily dogee which is good because
this is indicating that the market has
hit a high point and it has stopped the
market hit a high point and it stopped
now it can potentially start having a
reversal so you're seeing how the market
starts creating these different type of
patterns where you can almost predict
what's going to happen next so here you
can see that we had the daily doe at the
strong level of resistance and if I
actually come here and this level of
resistance I double tap this line this
box will pop up right here and this is
actually around psychological level
130,000 it's actually a little bit more
above than I would anticipate but you
can see right here round psychological
level
130,000 or like the smart money concept
guys would call it a bank Zone a order
block whatever [__] they want to say
it's a level of support and resistance
same [__] so we go over here now down to
the 1 hour and you can see how the 1
hour has created this strong level of
support here and what we are going to
literally wait for is this so as of
right now we have already had the push
down so I remove this leg on the push
down now we just need the actual break
of it so we need something like this
retest and then we'll be entering the
trade into the downside so GBP USD
currently loading Euro gvp next we have
this level of Interest right here
waiting for price to have the pullback
to head to the downside just simply
waiting for that to then make its way
and then lastly we have a GBP CAD which
where go and then gvp CAD which I just
found it it just got lost for whatever
reason is going to be the next pair and
as you can see we've had the continuous
push to the upside what we were looking
for mainly is on this 1 hour time frame
what we were waiting for is for price to
have a break and then a retest under
this level here so then we can actually
enter the trade to the downside so this
is basically a little bit similar to
gbpusd just look if you were to look at
gbpusd you to look at the market here
this is GBP CAD you look at gbpusd it
actually already had the push GBP CAD
hasn't had the push just yet so gbpusd
technically ahead of it that's why I'm
more interested in it so right now 1 in
the morning the only trade that we're
actually about to enter is GBP JPY and
that Candlestick did not close engulfing
so we have about 57 minutes for this
next Candlestick to close I'm going to
wait for it in about 57 minutes it's
going to be 2:00 in the
morning see if we enter the first trade
s and forget if not I'll see you guys
tomorrow in the morning all right guys
good morning it is currently July 16th
Tuesday morning so obviously we stayed
up last night it's about like 3: in the
morning is saas knocked out I stayed up
to catch this trade
and it was for no reason because let me
just explain so first of all let me show
you guys the marker right now so you
guys can see we are currently in the
position and this is literally the max
that I can honestly risk on the account
even if I wanted to enter a position
right now it would not let me because I
don't have enough leverage my leverage
right now is 1 to 500 so this is the max
that I can literally execute on the
market which is what is that like 1.2 L
so let me show you guys the market on
the trade so last night remember that I
explained to you guys that I was waiting
for the market to have a body closure
under this line right here so we had
that body engulfing Candlestick and then
I pretty much entered on the little
quick pull back of the next one and now
that was for no reason because all of
London session as soon as I fell asleep
literally did
nothing I'm on 3 hours of sleep for oh
let's show them the time currently it is
8:25 5 in the morning so what does that
mean that 3 and 1/2 hours it's an
amazing first day we're doing this again
we're doing this again we're doing this
again but the point is that now price is
pulling back into the area where we
entered usually what should happen is as
soon as we enter the trade it just goes
down with the momentum of the session
but not we haven't but it is what it is
enter the trade s forget my prediction
is that now from here it is going to go
down so this is basically what I want to
show you guys here is just basically
this candles look like it's pulling back
into that area but we're just going to
honestly set and forget next is GBP USD
we had a little bit of this break right
here that we were anticipating but if we
were to look at it on the 4H hour which
is this time frame right here we did not
have that body closure under this box
which really the Box should be right
around here but obviously on the 1 hour
it would be around this level we had the
break and on the retest no engulfing
Candlestick no trade that is the
importance of following the trading plan
you can literally stay up all night wait
3 days for the trade there's no entry no
trade as of right now this was not
executed because there was no
opportunity and then Euro GBP we're
waiting for the market to have its pull
back to this area which we are still
actively waiting for and then lastly gvp
CAD which you've had the push all the
way to the upside basically at this
point we have not had the break and
retest under here so we are still just
actively waiting the only position that
is actively live right now is GBP
JPY and all we got to do at this point
set and forget all right to update the
time it is currently 8:27 in the morning
Tuesday morning but I got it 1 minute
ago positive $15 now we are about to hit
Margin Call on the account 1 minute
later but this trading is so funny dude
oh my God all right so trade up there
right now it looks so as you guys can
see right here we are currently pretty
much about below the accounts we're
about 37% right now and uh looks like
this Candlestick is making highs right
now so that's a very strong 1 hour
bullish engulfing Candlestick oh oh oh
no yeah that's not good so if this that
Candlestick closes like that in the next
20 minutes because we have 20 minutes
left in this Candlestick closure we're
pretty much cooked cuz then the next
Candlestick would just and we're H we're
not even halfway to our stop loss and
we're already down pretty much a third
so you know cuz you have to you have to
count in spread commission and all that
[__] yeah if this trade goes up we're
cooked but it's okay cuz guess what we
just do it again it's just 100 bucks all
right guys market update I'm on the
camera right now Sebastian had to go do
whatever he had to go do trade is
looking well so this is a trade update
right now so we are currently sitting at
around
$131 in profit and the trade has
literally had a beautiful rejection from
this area right here we've had a little
bit of a pullback so that Candlestick
did end up indeed closing engulfing but
not above this structure point or that
one so that was good and now we're
pretty much just set and forgetting
gbpusd on the other hand which was the
other Market it literally had the retest
on the lower time frame and then it had
the push we're looking for that retest
on the higher time frame it just didn't
happen it happened on the lower time
frame spr but the movement is actually
happening Euro gvp still hasn't made it
here and then GBP CAD it is waiting
still for this break and retest to then
head to the downside but GJ which is a
trade that we are actively in right now
is looking very well and then the
current time right now is 12:49 p.m. so
as of right now set and forget probably
going to go eat right now and and then
potentially hit the gym had Zoom
meetings all day and then probably a
little bit more zoom meetings it's the
reality of my life lately just trade
meetings with the guys and then DM sleep
repeat fun life right sometimes it is
all right guys so trade upate it is
currently 4:00 in the afternoon and the
trade right now currently looks like
this so literally right around break
even the daily Candlestick is looking
like a bullish daily Candlestick 4 hours
looks like some bearish rejections and
then you can see right here that the
trade is literally break in so stayed up
got four hours of sleep for no reason
but we technically are winning a trade
today and we are up so today we get to
drive the Ferrari the days we don't make
money we drive the BR never made back
the days we make money we drive the
supercars cold start you ready
a
[Music]
usually what we do is we go hit aana or
run later we're going to go straight
home right now and run So currently it
is 5:00 in the
afternoon and probably go for probably
get home in like 20 25 minutes then go
for about a 25 minute
run running
sucks is [__] fat
got to do what you got to
do all right guys market update it is
currently 10:00 at night and the markets
are not looking that good the account is
not looking that good but it doesn't
matter we're going to set and forget
throughout the whole entire night we
don't have to stay up watching the
market we already stayed up to enter the
trade now we simply just set and forget
the trade either hits our stop loss or
hits our take profit so the account is
not looking that good right now you guys
can see that we are currently down about
$32 on the account and that is because
the daily time frame closes a bullish
Candlestick so as you guys can see right
here the daily bullish Candlestick was
very strong and it engulf this previous
one and the body still didn't make it to
these body structures right here so this
next daily Candlestick could simply go a
little bit higher than the other one the
4our has had two strong bullish
engulfing candlesticks which are not
well this is engulfing this is just a
bullish candle that is not good but what
does look good is the 1 hour so the 1
hour is clearly creating accumulation
and rejecting at this level we just
pretty much have to set and forget what
I really want from this Candlestick
right here and it's what it's looking
like it's doing even though it still has
53 minutes left for it to close we need
this Candlestick to close like a bearish
engulfing like this one so then that can
then give it the movement to the
downside so as right now we're currently
down
$35 on the challenge we just have to set
and forget and then wait for the market
to either go back into profit or simply
blow the account next is gbpusd so
gbpusd we had the little quick retest
earlier but we did not have the movement
to the downside because we had this pull
back above the area of Interest we want
to have the retest and then the
rejection under this level of support
and resistance then the daily time frame
close as a daily doe so I always am a
strong believer that these dois always
get that Wick fill you see this Wick
right here filled it see this Wick
filled now I believe we can fill this
Wick to the downside and then this is
where I'm going to be waiting for a
little break and retest under to
actually be able to be interested in
this trade so I'm going to be waiting
for something like this in order for us
to actually execute on this trade but
obviously I cannot enter this trade
because I maxed out margin on GP JPY so
I can't really do much other than just
let the other trade play out but just
updating you guys on what the markets
are doing lastly the rgbp is now on its
way to the area of Interest we haven't
quite made it there yet so there's
nothing that we can do and then GBP CAD
if you guys look at it on the 1 hour
time frame which is the time frame that
we're mainly looking at it we still
haven't had that break and retest under
so I am simply not interested at all
there's nothing that we can do GBP JPY
is what we're in right now we simply
have to do one thing and that is set and
forget so I'll see you guys tomorrow in
the in the morning and let's see how we
wake up with the account ladies and
gentlemen I'm sorry to announce
that we have reached the goal for the
week actively right now we are currently
up
$330 you guys can see here so last night
literally what I said happened once
again so look check it out GBP JPY right
after that 1 hour bearish engulfing
candles STI literally the whole momentum
throughout London session was that
bearish move to the downside had my
takeprofit set at a 1 to 3.4 Rich reward
so meaning if I risked 100 bucks here
then I would have made
$340 right here as you guys can see that
is literally the math that is happening
right now now some of you guys may be
asking yourselves why didn't the trade
take me out at my takeprofit point where
I have it well ladies and gentlemen that
is the whole point of set and forget I
don't ever actually put the tap take
profit numbers so I never actually plug
in this number because I want to
maximize the risk to reward that I get
on the trade I always put the stop- loss
cuz I want to cut my I want to cut my
losses short but I never want to cut my
profit short so even though we obviously
you know we're probably up like $600
$700 this trade then end up putting back
a little bit um so right now we are at
this point right here this trade is
giving us a 1.38 risk to reward
beautiful bearish move the trade played
out perfectly daily time frame you have
a beautiful bearish and golfing
Candlestick everything playing out
perfect so our goal for this week was to
turn $100 into $200 we're actually up
$400 so we just hit the target for this
week and for next week so we have a
whole week ahead which is pretty cool
next um just to show you guys a market
update on the other markets so this is
GBP JPY gbpusd as you can see we were
waiting for that break and retest under
to then sell we did not get that break
and retest under meaning we did not
enter the cell this is the importance of
patience no break and retest no entry
loss avoided this is the importantance
of having the trading plan and sticking
to it Euro GBP you guys can see I never
quite really made it into that zone so
we simply never executed the trade and
then GBP CAD same exact thing we were
waiting for a break and retest under in
order to sell we never got it we never
executed the trade this is the
importance of having a trading plan
ladies and gentlemen it does not get
more legit and more transparent than
that right there just to put you guys a
little into a perspective If This Were
to be $11,000 we would be up
$3,500 right now if this were to be
$110,000 we would be up
$335,000 and if this were to be a 100
Grand we would be up
$350,000 nothing changes in the market
only only thing that changes is how much
money you have in the account and how
much money you're risking this
Candlestick is going to close in 15
minutes over here so I want to see how
this Candlestick closes right here in 15
minutes and then based off of that I'll
then make my decision and let's see if
we can then this week flip this
$450 to then $800 or $900 because that
would put us really really really fast
into the margin that we need to be in
order for us to flip the $100 to the
mail a lot faster so keep you up
there so trade update right now it is
currently 2:30 in the afternoon pretty
much we closed at a
$437 in profit you guys can see it here
on the
[__]
[Music]
[Applause]
look there's fans everywhere here in
Miami I love you guys trust me I have so
much love for the fans all like
literally you guys know where I live
it's [__] crazy but we're here
showing you guys the account you guys
can see here the my effects book pretty
much how it's looking currently up
$437 these are pretty much the fees we
got to pay these are the orders or
there's nothing open right now this is
the history though you guys can see here
both positions that we ended up taking
that's the profit that we Clos in and
now same [__] gym time no it sucks so
you only get to drive one Supercar now
Lamborghini twin turbo just sold it
whyde body yours is at the shop the rear
brake caliper is broken they're fixing
it the Porsche I blew the second gear on
the Porsche
drifting uh rollsroyce is finally
getting done wrapped should be done
today or tomorrow what other C do I have
the May back I'm not going to drive oh
yeah oh I sold the Scat Pack got rid of
the Scat Pack Scat Pack is gone that was
probably the dumbest thing I ever bought
yeah the side by side the side by side
is in the shop as well bro half of my
fleet right now is in the shop I only
get to drive a Ferrari right now [__]
[Music]
[Applause]
all right guys market update it is
currently Wednesday night 11:47 p.m. and
you guys can clearly see the account is
currently at
$437 now you might be asking yourself am
I going to keep trading am I going to
stop trading H well my goal for for this
week was to turn $100 into 200 and then
next week 200 to 400 so technically I
reached the goal for this week and for
next week what would you do let me know
in the comments below would you stop
trading for the week and next week or
would you look for other opportunities
just for the lower risk that's what I'm
thinking right now I don't want to stop
trading because there's there's great
opportunities in the market why should I
just simply not take them I might just
take them but obviously instead of
risking the higher amount that I was
supposed to I'm going to risk simply
half that much because I'm on tracks I'm
I'm literally ahead of the time that I
have planned to pass 100 to the mil let
me just show you guys a little bit of
the market so this is the beauty of
having a beautiful Trend continuation
pattern this trade if I would have
continued hold all the way to this point
would have gave me a one to8 meaning I
would have turned the $100 to $800 in
one single move without doing anything I
would have literally saved 3 weeks on
one move but obviously I'm sticking to
my plan so as of right now this this
Market is actively having a pullback to
what looks to be like this level of
resistance right here but I'm not really
that interested on GBP JPY anymore we
got the money from it and we're pretty
much gone the next Market is we have is
gbpusd we've clearly had a break to the
upside and as of right now I am not
interested in anything on gbpusd other
than this break and retest under Euro
GBP this is the one that I'm liking
right now because it is approaching this
area of interest on this PR previous
structure level so we finally have our
well we haven't made it just yet we're
getting there very soon so now I'm going
to be waiting for either a bearish and
golfing Candlestick from this level here
so then we can sell and then GBP CAD we
never had the break and retest under so
what I do is I come over to this section
right here now and I'm going to put Euro
GBP as my number one pair that I'm going
to be simply interested in which is a
bearish engulfing Candlestick here
something like this engulfing here this
engulfing in here this and go in here so
all we have to do is be patient my trade
London session again today we're just
going to lower our risk so that being
said it's day three going way better
than the last challenge to start off and
all I got to say is set and forget all
right guys good morning trade up there
right now it is currently 9:21 in the
morning uh pretty much nothing really
happened last night let me show you guys
it looks like it's happening right now
so last night we were anticipating for
this Candlestick right here to have a
bearish engulfing Candlestick under this
candle to then enter the trade we're
pretty much looking for something like
this right once it did engulf our stop
loss would have been around here and
then we would have sold luckily we wait
for that entry signal you have to wait
for the entry signal no entry signal no
trade what do we do we avoided a loss so
this right here is a prime example of
patient paace but now it looks like
we've actually perfectly tapped into
this area of Interest here on the daily
time frame you can see a daily Wick is
currently creating and now if this 4our
Candlestick closes under this
Candlestick right here pretty much under
here then I would be interested in then
entering this trade this Candlestick
will take about another 4 hours to close
because this is a 4H hour Candlestick so
we have to remain very patient GBP JPY
literally did nothing you guys can see
here that obviously throughout the night
we just decided to have another little
pullback we just pretty much slowed down
uh gbpusd we did have a little bit more
of a retracement but once again the only
way I'll take this trade is if we do
this and then GBP CAD just not even
interested at all we could dish it for
the week the only one we're interested
in right now is Euro GBP so patience
patience pays and this is exactly what
experience gives you waiting for that
entry signal waiting for it to hit the
area of interest just avoided the loss I
could have literally just blown the
account if I wasn't a little of a
paycheck so actively right now it is
9:32 in the morning the account is
currently sitting at
$437 Still Still exactly the same now
let's wait see what the market
[Music]
do you're looking like a shorter version
of Mike
thirst mik my boy all right guys mark
update it is currently Friday 1 in the
morning so pretty much today no trading
volume spent the majority of the day
just home pretty much what I do every
single day currently the market is still
exactly the same I mean the account is
still exactly the same let me show you
guys the market though so earlier today
we were waiting for price to have a
bearish engulfing Candlestick under this
line right here we did not have that so
we did not take the trade uh daily time
frame did not close with a daily
rejection so there's nothing that we can
do GBP py did start having a little bit
of a pullback pretty much how we
anticipated but I'm not interested in it
gbpusd has officially broken under now
we're going to wait for a little retest
to then head to the upside we did have a
little bit of a quick retest here but
not quite what I would want I want to
have something like this retest bearish
candle and then enter so we're got to
wait for this pullback this might be
ready for next week and then GBP CAD
just hasn't really done anything so
let's see if we can get GBP USD to have
that pullback tonight during London if
not we'll take it in the last couple of
hours of New York on Friday obviously
not too close to Market close if not
worst case pretty much done trading for
the week I'll update you guys in the
morning and see how it goes and just
like that the week has come to an end
this has been probably one of the best
starts to the 100 to the m challenge
that I could have probably ever asked
for but before I do a recap let me just
show you guys how the markets closed off
so you guys can see here that Euro GBP
we did not have the bearish engulfing
candles stick at this point or at at
this point so we never actually entered
this trade at all and this is key and
I'm showing you guys how you can avoid a
loss being involved in the market is not
how you make money in the market it's
actually avoiding the unnecessary trades
to be involved in the market so less is
more in trading next is GBP JPY you can
see our trade pretty much didn't pull
back exactly where we wanted to to enter
again but we already made the money that
we had to on the trade that we took so
we just set up forget that market gbpusd
did not retest this level to then sell
so we never took the trade and then GBP
CAD never had the break and reach the
under so then we never took the trade
this is a prime example showing you guys
how patience pays and it's going to be
the key to making money in this
Challenge and successfully flipping the
challenge so you guys saw to give you
guys a little bit of a recap how we
traded this week and how I plan to
continue to trade for the rest of this
challenge at the beginning of the week
we analyzed the markets on Sunday Swings
with students and we picked out the top
three top four pairs that we're going to
trade for the week and the most
aggressive one was going to be GBP JPY
because it was a counter Trend trade
because we're trading against the trend
but you can almost predict that the
market is going to have that pullback
because of a reversal pattern shift of
structure break of structure EMA candles
rejection all these different types of
confluences that give you more of a
reason to enter the sell versus the buy
with the market and the market almost
needed that sell then after we took that
trade we said and forget got about a 1
to four risk reward on the trade which
is amazing cuz it actually set us above
our takeprofit goal for for the week the
goal for the week was 200 bucks we got
it up to $437 which is literally double
of what we predicted but then after that
instead of calling it a week we pretty
much looked for another trade
opportunity to enter the market which is
going to be Euro GBP which was hopefully
take the account from 400 to 800 but we
did not take the trade because we had to
wait for that specific entry signal so
we took a trade and then we avoided a
loss later down that week because we
remain patient and we follow the set and
forget strategy if you want to know more
about the set and forget strategy where
it lets me find markets just like these
click the link in the description below
because that is exactly where I host
cause every single Sunday with my
students and I'm sharing the trades that
I am actively going to be trading during
the 100 to the mail with them every
single Sunday I give them the markets
that I am going to be trading during the
hundred to the maill so they can have
the same exact results as me and they
can flip their accounts and do whatever
they want to do with their own funds
because these markets are giving amazing
opportunities and I'm sharing it with my
students every single Sunday I get on a
call with them and I share these trades
with them when they join the set and
forget community so you want to know
more about it click the link in the
description below so you can see what
the CER forget Community is about but
with that being said this is pretty much
a wrap of week one of the 100 to the
mill challenge make sure you guys hit
that subscribe button because this is
only getting started and I can see this
going very very very far this time very
confident and I'm more excited than ever
to do this challenge appreciate you guys
watching this video all the way to the
end I'll see you guys in the next one